Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 18, folder: (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Folks 'n' Facts, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: the toughest job in the world, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Sidney Hyman. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Delco Radio Broadcaster, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: The GM Information Rack Service In Brief, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Helping Dealersmake more and better friends, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: GM Topics, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: The GM Information Rack Service In Brief, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: News Breaker, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Guide Light, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: The B.O.P. Beacon, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    March 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: "Inside AC" Special, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    September 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Clan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By C. E. Wilson. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: aids to Educators, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: An Automobile Man Looks Ahead, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. December 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: An Address By James M. Roche, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. March 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Fulfilling America's Aspirations-Our Individual Responsibility, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. March 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Special Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: The Responsibilities of Freedom, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. May 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Annual Public Service Award Dinner The Advertising Council, Inc., Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. December 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: New Engineering Priorities For The '70s, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Edward N. Cole. January 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Preserving And Renewing Our Environment, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Richard C. Gerstenberg. March 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Try This Magic Quiz About GM, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: How You Can Make Friends for General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: Report on the Golden Milestone Contest, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: A New Paradox, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Edward N. Cole. December 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Industry's Role In Environmental Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By E.N. Cole. February 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: "The Heart Of The MatterIs Opportunity", Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Richard C. Gerstenberg. November 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: "We are all the beneficiaries of business.", Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. October 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Let's Tell The Story of Profit, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Richard C. Gerstenberg. December 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Price Stability-An Attainable Goal?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. February 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Making Free Enterprise Free, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By James M. Roche. January 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: "The Role Of Business In Solving Social Problems", Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Anthony G. De Lorenzo. November 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Open House, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 53: GM lives here, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: GMH People, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: The Road to better Living, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 56: reflector, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 57: people, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 58: News and Views, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 59: Making Friends For GM In The Plant Community, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Information Handbook, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 61: General Motors Information Handbook for 1964, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Box: 18, folder: (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Expanding Employment The Answer To Unemployment, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
    By Louis G. Seaton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Challenge of Engineering's Second 100 Years, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 3-Year GM Peace, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Wheels For A Waiting World, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
    By Christy Borth. Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Free Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Story of General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Story of General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Box: 18, folder: (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: hi there, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: A Six Point Objective for General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Box: 18, folder: (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Look At GM, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Ten Years of Industrial Peace at GM, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Text of reply of General Motors President, Harlow H. Curtice, to Walter P. Reuther, President, UAW, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    August 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: A Message To Our Employes On Progress Of The Strike Situation, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. January 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: General Motors And The Strike Conference, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The Story of the General Motors Strike, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: How GM Operates Without UAW Pact, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: General Motors' Statement Before Fact-Finding Board, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Free Collective Bargaining Works!, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Labor Relations In General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: A Message To Our Employes On Progress Of The Strike Situation, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: How Do GM Wages Stack Up?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Labor Relations in General Motors and The Story Behind the Five-Year Agreements, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: The Responsibility of Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    July 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: GM and its People An American Industrial Team, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: What Can You Count On?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Free Collective Bargaining Works!, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: GM Statement of Wage Policy: 1948, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: What Can You Count On?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Employe Relations In General Motors, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Planning today for tomorrow's progress 1953 personel and employe relations conference, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: General Motors Reply to UAW-CIO Brief, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    November 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Six Basic General Motors Principles, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Grievance Procedure, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: How GM Operates Without UAW Pact, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Box: 19, folder: 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your Extra Benefits, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: GM Educational Opportunities, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Working With General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: To Help Pay Your Bills, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Insurance Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Your Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: To Employes Whose Monthly Base Salaries Are $800 Or More, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Group Travel Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Your GM Insurance Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Your future with Buick, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Educational Assistance for GM Employes, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Spare Time Training Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Appointment to Opportunity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: your GM pension, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    September 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The 1958 Sub Plan At GM, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Your Extra Benefits, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: The Improved General Motors Insurance Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Your Gm Income Security Plan, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Employe Relations In General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By Vern Proctor. May 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: How Divisions Conduct Management Meetings, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Your Benefits, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Motors Policies And Progress, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Winter, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The College Graduate And General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Imagination, Money and Satisfaction, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Your Job with Delco Morraine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Working with General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Tuning in, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Working with Brown Lipe Chapin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Can I be a Craftsman?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: More Power To You, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Working with General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: your Job at Ternstedt, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: GM The College Graduate And General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Employe Service Recognition, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Working With General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Opening The Door To Opportunity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: what you should know about your Benefits, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    November 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: MJC Accentuating the Positive, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: "I'm with GM, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Organization of General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Development And Growth of General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. December 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Economic Impact of the Multinational Corporation, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. February 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Let's Tell The Story of Profit, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: "Management's Responsibility for Discipline", Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By H. W. Anderson. May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Adventures of the Inquiring Mind, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Where Today Meets Tomorrow, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Expanding Employment The Answer To Unemployment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By Louis G. Seaton. November 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: General Motors Policies and Practices, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: a better way, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The Organization of General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: the time between, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Story of General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Look at General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: How Do GM Wages Stack Up?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Education of Employees For Retirement, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: A Big Help, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: A Big Help, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Information Concerning the UAW-CIO Strike at General Motors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    December 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Harrison Radiator Division, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: "The Personnel Function In Profile", Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By I. Dent Jenkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Working Together, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: the hyatt..Family, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your Job with Morraine Products, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: you and your job at New Departure, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Recognition of Loyalty & Service at New Departure, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Serving Our Employes New Departure Personnel Department, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The story of Pontiacand your job, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Your Performance On The Record, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: General Motors Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: General Telephone Company of California 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: 1965 Annual Report General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc., Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: 1963 Annual Report General Telephone Co. of Indiana, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    January 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Indiana General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Green Castle, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Global Communications, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Wabash, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: 1961 General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. Annual Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Good Government, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    October 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News from Gne, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: What's Youd Idea, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Inventor of the Telephone, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: General Telephone Co. of Indiana 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: A Real Cover Story, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: 65 Yearsof Automatic Telephony, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: About Your Company An Employee Opinion Survey, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By C. H. Lawshe. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    July 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: General News, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Index, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: General Instruction No. 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Corporate History of Predecessor and Acquired Companies, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: 25 years of growing with Indiana, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: General Instruction No. 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. Organization Charts, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Our Code of Business Ethics, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: General Instruction No. 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Box: 19, folder: (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: General, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: executive and general offices, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Practices and Standards For the Personnel Department, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: A Career Awaits You in the traffic department, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: person toperson, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Index, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
    March 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: History of Conveersion Factors, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Summary of Non-Productive Hours and Amount Paid For, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Summary of Non-Productive Hours and Amount Paid For, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: During 1961, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Wages and Salaries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Company Average Percent Increases Given To Salaried Employees At or Above Base Rates, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Employee Transfer, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Working Rules For Hourly Non-Union Employees, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Box: 20, folder: 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Company-IBEW Reach Agreement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: In the Matter of the Arbitration Between General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    August 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Award of Arbitration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance For Employees, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Your Major Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Plan for Employees' Pensions, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. Organization Charts, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Tuition Aid Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Your Major Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance For Employees, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Pension Plan for General Telephone employees, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Application For Tuition Aid, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Plan for Employees' Pensions, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: An Invitation To shape your own future at General Telephone, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: you can grow., Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Policy Book, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Management Orientation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Policy Statement on Political Activity, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: General Telephone Corporation Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: annual report 1956, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    March 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Union Agreement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    November 26-June 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industry's Report on Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Hood's, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Personnel Administration In Georgia State Government, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Personnel Administration In Georgia State Government, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    January 7. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Georgia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: How Do I Handle A Grievance, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Employee Relations Institute, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Gerber News, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Gerber News, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Gerber News, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1954, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Highlights of Your Increased Benefits In the Gerber Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: When You Retire, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Gerber's Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Gerber's Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Gerber Retirement Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Application for Employment with Gerber's Baby Foods, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Application For Employment with Gerber Products Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Gerber's Baby Foods Application For Employment-Factory, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Gillette Company Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Opportunities For Engineers At Gillette, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Career Opportunities in Financial Management, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Opportunities In Marketing, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Gillette Safety Razor Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Gillette Safety Razor Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Careers with Gillette Safety Razor Company in manufacturing, Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Whom Do You Believe?, Publication (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Glass Containers, Publication (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Box: 20, folder: (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Glass Containers 1968, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Billions of Bottles, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Glass Containers 1964, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: A Close-Up of Closures, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
    By Alfred Lief. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Story of Glass Containers, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Books and Booklets On Old Glass, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Glass Containers 1967, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: "Report of Progress", Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
    By Roger H. Hetzel. May 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Glass Containers 1956, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Glass Containers 1970 Edition, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)